

ADDRESS

Krebsevej 68, 2650 Hvidovre

PHONE

+45 5030 9996

EMAIL

mptijeglic@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mar tina-peck-tijeglic/

LANGUAGE

Croatian – Native speaker English – Highly proficient Danish – Very good command

PERSONAL SKILLS

Organizational skills Inclusive leadership Attention to details Customer focus

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Granta Edu Pack Solidworks TIA portal RoboDK Enterprise Dynamic Microsoft Office Illustrator

INTERESTS

Arts and Crafts Gardening Cycling Reading

MARTINA PECK - TIJEGLIC

PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT

SUMMARY

Student at KEA focused on production technology where ideas are born and realized through specific methods and teamwork. Within study and work experience I have gained valuable lessons in optimizing and prioritizing, teamwork, and communication.

EDUCATION

KEA - Copenhagen school of design and technology, Denmark

Academy Profession in Production Technology

August 2021 - Present

Faculty of Textile Technology, Zagreb, Croatia

Master's degree in Industrial Design

Prize for the best innovation in sport and recreation at INOVA 2018 October 2015 – July 2018

Faculty of Textile Technology, Zagreb, Croatia

Bachelor's degree in Textile Technology October 2010 – July 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Acacie Blomster - Floral Assistant; Farum, Denmark

Tasks and responsibilities:

- communicating with customers
- arranging decorations and taking care of the plants
- optimizing work

May 2020-Present

Index.hr - Journalist; Zagreb, Croatia

Tasks and responsibilities:

- conducting research and interviews to uncover interesting and significant news

September 2019–February 2020

Vesna Sposa - Public Relations Specialist; Zagreb, Croatia

Tasks and responsibilities:

- formulating PR plans and strategies (Newsletters, social media, Blog, articles)
- customer focus within entertainment industry, journalists and fashion houses
- optimizing work for more efficient business results Mar 2018–Sep 2019

COURSES

Danish Language School at UCplus – Oct 2020 – July 2022 Communication School at Logos Education – Feb 2016 – Sep 2016

ACTIVITIES

Volunteer at SDP (Social Democratic Party) – Zagreb, Croatia – 2007 - 2018